yesemails.com 2010-11-07

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at http://www.yesemails.com/. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for http://www.yesemails.com/. 

Log Files 

We may use log files to track visits to http://www.yesemails.com/. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personal identifiable information. 

Cookies 

This site does not use cookies. However, Advertising services such Google Adsense use cookies on http://www.yesemails.com/. We have no access to and can not control these cookies. 

What is a Cookie? 

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. 

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. 

Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you. 

There are two different types of cookies: 

1) Session Cookies: These are temporary and are erased when you close your browser at the end of your surfing session. The next time you visit that particular site it will not recognise you and will treat you as a completely new visitor as there is nothing in your browser to let the site know that you have visited before. 

2) Persistent Cookies: These remain on your hard drive until you erase them or they expire. How long a cookie remains on your browser depends on how long the visited website has programmed the cookie to last. 

Beacons 

This site does not use beacons. However, Advertising services such Google Adsense use cookies on http://www.yesemails.com/. We have no access to and can not control these beacon logs. 

What is a Beacon? 

A beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. 

For example a company owning a network of sites may use web beacons to count and recognise users travelling around its network. Being able to recognise you enables the site owner to personalise your visit and make it more user friendly. 

Outgoing Links 

http://www.yesemails.com/ may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware that when they leave http://www.yesemails.com/ to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by http://www.yesemails.com/. 

Advertisers and Affiliate Companies 

http://www.yesemails.com/ uses outside ad companies to display ads, such as Google Adsense. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. To the best of our knowledge, we follow all ad and affiliate company privacy policies. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email [emails@yesemails.com](mailto:emails@yesemails.com)
